# TOMMY KNIGHT

## **CURRICULUM VITAE**

## CONTACT

07568392007

tknighted@hotmail.com

Southend, SS1 1JF

www.TommyK.uk

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Dev Bootcamp Strive School Apr - Oct 2021

A Levels SJW Mathematical School Math, Chemistry, Biology, Art 2009/11

GCSE's

SJW Mathematical School

15 A\* - B

2007/09

#### **SKILLS**

- Teamwork / Communication
- Working under pressure
- Time Management
- Advanced Computer Literacy
- Cash Handling

#### **INTERESTS**

Film, Music, Computer Coding, Cooking, Esports, Skateboarding, Bouldering, Team Sports, Travelling, Art, Charity work.

#### **PROFILE**

As a proffesional actor with over 20 years of experience in the entertainment industry, I have been fortunate to work on numerous productions in the West End, Theatre, Film, and Television. My extensive background in performing has not only exposed me to a wealth of talented and dedicated professionals, but has also inspired me to pursue my passion for building full-stack web applications in my free time. With over 60 productions under my belt, I am changing direction to now seek a long-term and consistent opportunity where I can utilize my unique skill set to make a meaningful contribution.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **ACTOR**

SELF EMPLOYED | UK, USA | 1999 - 2021

My most notable work includes; Doctor Who (BBC), Waterloo Road (BBC), The Sarah Jane Adventures (CBBC), Victoria (ITV), Glue (E4), The Hippopotamus (Film). I have also been involved in many script writing workshops with the National Theatre, events for Red Nose Day, Comic Relief and multiple Sci-Fi conventions across the world.

CUSTOMER TECHNICAL SUPPORT AGENT VENTRICA | SOUTHEND-ON-SEA | 2022 - 2023

I worked at Ventrica's office to provide support for Ferrero with Thorntons website and the Kinder Egg recall of April 2022. I handled many different types of data mostly using Excel and Zendesk, raised tickets based on feedback of technical issues and consumer purchases.

Contact Kayleigh Richards

01702 445860

#### **BARISTA**

ROCHESTER COFFEE CO. | ROCHESTER | 2019 - 2021

Excelled in customer service as a full-time barista at a local independent coffee shop. Skillfully crafted coffee drinks, sandwiches, and toasties, built strong relationships with customers to create a warm and welcoming atmosphere while maintaining a pristine and welcoming venue. Efficiently managed closing procedures, cashing up and closing the shop at the end of the day.

Contact Abi Brett

07833612030

#### CHEF

MICAWBERS FISH BAR & RESTAURANT | ROCHESTER | 2016 - 2017

Balanced serving and culinary responsibilities as a Chef and Server at a busy restaurant. Preparing a diverse range of menu items, including full English breakfasts, omelets, burgers, and signature fried fish and chips. Efficiently managed high-pressure situations, multitasking to take orders and serve customers in a fast-paced environment.

Contact Dorean Smith

07896277870